careersnigeria.com 2017-02-23

# Privacy Policy-Latest Jobs in Nigeria

Revised: January, 2015  

Questions or suggestions arising from this policy should be directed to [info@jobberman.com](mailto:info@jobberman.com) 

All information regarding a job offer is from sources deemed reliable. No representation is made as to the accuracy thereof, and such information is subject to errors, omission, and change of details without notice. 

 **JOBBERMAN’s Privacy Statement**

JOBBERMAN is a job search and career development company operating in the online career space in Nigeria. JOBBERMAN is very sensitive to privacy issues. Any user information we collect is considered private and we do not use, or share it except as permitted herein, without the user's permission. We use this personal information at JOBBERMAN to provide the best quality service possible. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by web addresses in the [jobberman.com](mailto:jobberman.com), [www.jobberman.com.gh](http://www.jobberman.com.gh/) and www.jobbermanlearning.com domains, which is hereafter referred to collectively as JOBBERMAN. We believe it is important you know how we treat the information you may provide to us.

 **Definitions**

This Statement has been prepared by JOBBERMAN Limited.

JOBBERMAN owns and operates the website located at www.jobberman.com (across desktop, mobile, tablet and apps and including any subdomains) ("the Site"). This Statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Site.

JOBBERMAN’s wholly owned subsidiaries, JOBBERMAN Ghana and JOBBERMAN Learning own and operate the websites located at [www.jobberman.com.gh](http://www.jobberman.com.gh/) and www.jobbermanlearning.com respectively across desktop, mobile, tablet and apps (including any subdomains).

In this Statement, any reference to “JOBBERMAN", "we", "us" and "our" includes a reference to JOBBERMAN Limited, JOBBERMAN Ghana and JOBBERMAN Learning.

Users who log on to the Site but do not create an account are referred to generically in this Statement as "users" or "you".

Users who register on the Site to obtain services offered by JOBBERMAN are referred to as "Registered Users". Unless the context provides otherwise, references in this Statement to "users" or "you" include references to generic users and Registered Users.

 **Information Collected by JOBBERMAN**

JOBBERMAN collects user information from several areas of the site without limitation, including the 'Membership Registration' area, which sections of the Site are most frequently visited, how often, and for how long. Data are always used as aggregated information, and may be shared with JOBBERMAN partners to provide them with information relating to how JOBBERMAN visitors 'use' the Site. 

**IP Addresses & Cookies**

JOBBERMAN tracks the IP address of a user's computer or place a "cookie" in the browser files of a user's computer. This is required by JOBBERMAN’s services to provide automated features. IP address and cookie log data is analyzed to better understand traffic flows and user preferences.

 **Collecting information on JOBBERMAN Registered Users**

As part of registering with JOBBERMAN, we collect personal information about Registered Users in order for Registered Users to take full advantage of JOBBERMAN's services. To do this, it will be necessary for Registered Users to provide additional information to JOBBERMAN.

 **Registration**

Registration on the Site is completely optional, but you need to register on the Site in order to submit a job application. To become a Registered User you will need to submit some personal information including your email address. You may access your information at any time by clicking 'My Account' on 'the Site' after signing into the Site.

 **Storing your CV**

Registered Users may elect to store their CV in their 'My Account' area, and use the CV when applying for a job. Deleting a CV from the 'My Account' area will mean it is no longer accessible to the Registered User. Deleted records may still be stored by JOBBERMAN in testing or backup systems for a period of time.

 **JOBBERMAN Profile**

All Registered Users have a personal JOBBERMAN Profile ('JOBBERMAN Profile') upon successful registration. A JOBBERMAN Profile can include a CV, personal information, employment and educational history, contact details, minimum salary expectations, skills, preferred job specializations and locations. Advertisers are able to search JOBBERMAN's Profile database to find and contact relevant candidates.

Registered Users can modify their CV at any time, or modify their personal, education and work experience details in relation to their JOBBERMAN Profile at any time, by going to the Profile area of the Site.

 **Use of Information Collected:**

Collected information helps JOBBERMAN understand its users' needs better, in order to improve its product and service offerings. Personal information may be used to contact users for the purpose of research, product development, marketing, or customer service, if the user has opted to receive such communication. JOBBERMAN may make personal information on CVs as well as other supplied information available to recruiters on a need basis where the intended use is to make available job opportunities to users. JOBBERMAN will not be held liable for any alternative use of such information by any individual or organization. User search activity is collected and analyzed and may be utilized by JOBBERMAN in the aggregate or in the abstract for a variety of business purposes.

 **Online Applications**

Making an online application to a job advertisement on JOBBERMAN is a free service that requires registration (to become a Registered User). Job applications require users to complete mandatory fields (first name, last name, phone, email, location, year of experience and latest employment) so that the Advertiser can identify and contact the applicant. Registered Users have the option of easily applying with a saved CV and uploading a cover letter.

This information may also be disclosed to JOBBERMAN's service providers and contractors from time to time who assist us to deliver our products and services.

By applying to a position advertised on JOBBERMAN you are requesting that JOBBERMAN pass the information to the relevant Advertiser. Any questions you have relating to a position advertised on JOBBERMAN, your online application and/or the status of your application should be directed to the Advertiser or their nominated agent, not JOBBERMAN. JOBBERMAN's role in the online application process is limited to forwarding your online application to the Advertiser, and storing it on their behalf (if requested to do so).

 **Use of Email Tools**

Upon registration, you may decide to subscribe for some offerings e.g. news, promotional materials. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters and promotional communications from JOBBERMAN, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in our newsletters, communication materials, or by emailing us at [info@jobberman.com](mailto:info@jobberman.com).

 **Opt-Out Policy:**

We offer visitors to the Site a means for controlling the use of session information. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering our services, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about the use of information volunteered by you, please send us a request specifying your new choice to tech.support@jobberman.com. 

To opt out of marketing or promotional emails, please either click 'unsubscribe' in the body of the email communication or go to [edit your JOBBERMAN profile](http://www.jobberman.com/applicant/profile "Edit profile link"), under 'My Account', then click Account Settings and select your preference(s).

 **Shared information:**

JOBBERMAN makes every possible effort to preserve user privacy; we may however need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the process of conducting our business transactions.

JOBBERMAN does not sell, rent, or lease user information to any third party, except stated otherwise (such as is in the case of CVs). While JOBBERMANendeavors to ensure the highest level of standards with a similar respect for user privacy, JOBBERMAN cannot be responsible for losses or damages that can result from a third party.

 **Security of personal information:**

JOBBERMAN takes every reasonable precaution to secure personal information within both its computers and its physical premises.

The security of your personal information is central to JOBBERMAN. We follow global industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and receipt. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at [info@jobberman.com](mailto:privacy@jobberman.com).

 **JOBBERMAN Partners & Advertisers**

JOBBERMAN discloses and/or makes available online applications to third parties and/or their nominees. The use of your information (personal or otherwise) by these third parties is not within the control of JOBBERMAN and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of these companies. This is also the case in respect of a JOBBERMAN Profile that has been provided by JOBBERMAN to an Advertiser in accordance with the paragraph above, 'JOBBERMAN Profile'.

Advertisers that place job ads on JOBBERMAN are asked by JOBBERMAN to comply with all relevant obligations relating to the use and disclosure of personal information that are outlined in the Privacy Act. JOBBERMAN cannot however guarantee compliance with these obligations.

 **Data Transfers**

Sometimes, we transfer information to 3rd party contractors including persons outside Nigeria. By giving us your personal information, you consent to such disclosures. Where we transfer information to persons outside Nigeria we believe that the recipients of such information are subject to a law, binding scheme or contract which effectively upholds principles for fair handling of the information that are similar in all material respects to international laws.

 **Changes to personal information:**

You may correct or update your personally identifiable information by making the change on your member account. If you no longer desire our service, you may deactivate your membership by sending an email to [info@jobberman.com](mailto:contracts@jobberman.com).

 **Changes to this Privacy Statement:**

If JOBBERMAN decides to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

JOBBERMAN reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
